A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner 2002-2006
The Library of Virginia
42409, 42410, 42411, 42412, 42413, 42414, 42421
88.73 cu. ft.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Office of the Governor, Patrick Henry Building, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia, 23219. Accessions 42409-42414 transferred 12 January 2006 and accessioned on 17 January 2006; Accession 42421 transferred on 18 January 2006 and accessioned on 19 January 2006.
Historical Information
The Policy Office is a division of the Office of the Governor in the Executive Branch of Virginia state Government. Members of the Policy Office include Policy Director, Deputy Policy Director, Counselor to the Governor, Deputy Counselor to the Governor, Policy Analysts and Special Assistant to the Governor. The Policy Office during Governor Mark R. Warner's administration (2002-2006) was responsible for the formation of policy, regulator and legislative review, and legal activities. On 8 January 2002, Governor-elect Warner chose Jane N. Kusiak, then Deputy Director of the Warner Transition Office, to serve as Director of Policy. She was responsible for developing the policies and legislative priorities of the Governor's Office. Kusiak left the Warner administration in September 2002. Robert M. Blue, Counselor to the Governor, also became Director of Policy following Kusiak's resignation. He served until May 2005 when he resigned to take a position with Dominion Resources, Inc. Suzette P. Denslow, who joined the Warner administration in 2002 as Deputy Policy Director, served as Policy Director from May 2005 until September 2005. William L. Murray, served as Deputy Director of Policy in 2002 and from 2003 to 2005, served as Policy Directory from 16 September 2005 to January 2006. Robert P. Crouch, Jr., Deputy Secretary of Public Safety, became Counselor to the Governor in May 2005. Other Policy Office staff members were: William L. Murray, David Hallock, Steven Gould, Ryan Childress, Wayne Turnage, Annal Healy, Jeff Bourne, Gail Jaspen, and Richard E. Williams.
Scope and Content
The Policy Office Records of Governor Mark R. Warner are housed in 253 boxes. The collection is arranged into five (5) series. Series have been designated for: I. Decision Briefs; II. Regulations; III. Legislative Files; IV. Policy Analyst Files; and V. Legal Files. These records include decision briefs, correspondence, memorandums, legislative files, briefing books, subject files, reports, settlement, warrants and legal files. These records document the legislative and policy priorities of the Warner administration (2002-2006).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. Decision Briefs, 2002-2005
II. Regulations, 2002-2006
III. Legislative Files, 2002-2005
IV. Policy Analyst Files, 2002-2006
V. Legal Files, 2002-2005
Contents List
- I. Decision Briefs, 2002-2005 (accession 42411)., Extent: 0.88 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  The Decision Briefs series is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged chronologically by year. Within each year, the records are filed in reverse chronological order. The series consists of decision briefs, requests, recommendations, background information and supporting documents including correspondence and legislative citations.
  This series documents Governor Warner's responses to requests from Executive Branch agencies for expenditure of funds from various sources controlled by the Governor's Office and approval of bond sales. Each Decision Brief usually includes: a description of the request including background material, discussion, and conclusions by the Policy Office; a recommendation from Richard D. Brown, Director, Department of Planning and Budget; and concurrence from Secretary of Finance John M. Bennett, the cabinet secretary overseeing requesting agency, and the Director of Policy (Jane N. Kusiak, 2002, Robert M. Blue, 2002-2005, and Suzette Denslow, 2005), Counselor to the Governor (Robert M. Blue, 2002-2005 and Robert Crouch, 2005-2006) and Chief of Staff (William H. Leighty, 2002-2006). If all concur, the Governor then signs the brief.
  Notable decision briefs include: Department of Motor Vehicles redesign of vehicle registration renewal form (17 October 2002), renovation of the Finance and Washington Buildings (2003), State Corporation Commission expenses in the case of Falwell v. Miller (9 September 2003), City of Poquoson for Hurricane Isabel damage (9 September 2004 and 5 August 2005), Department of Emergency Management for Tropical Storm Gaston disaster costs (25 October 2004), Department of Emergency Management for Hurricane Isabel recovery (May 2004) and Tazewell Flood of 2001 (May 2004), Department of Medical Assistance for emergency spending for victims of Hurricane Katrina (5 October 2005), and Department of Emergency Management, Southwest Virginia Flood of November 2003 (26 April 2005) and Tropical Depression Jeanne (24 February 2005).
  Decision Briefs related to bond sales include: Commonwealth of Virginia Transportation Revenue and Refunding Bonds, Virginia Housing and Development Authority Housing Bonds, Virginia College Building Authority Bonds, Virginia Resources Authority Bonds, General Obligation Bonds, Virginia Commonwealth University Revenue Pledge Bonds, Virginia Public Building Authority Facilities Revenue and Refunding Bonds, 9 c Higher Educational Institutions Bonds, and Virginia Small Business Financing Authority.
  - 2002
    - DEQ consent decree with U.S. Interior and Certus, Inc. (Octocure spill into Clinch River in Tazewell County), 27 December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Attorney General - Legal Defense Fund for Virginia v. Maryland, 27 December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind at Staunton, 27 December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Pubic School Authority (VPSA) 1997 Resolution Certification, December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Treasury - general obligation refunding bonds, November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Transportation Revenue and Refunding Bonds, November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Roanoke Tire Fire from VEERF, 8 November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Small Business Financing Authority (VSBFA) Bonds, November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Historic Resources - Survey and Planning Cost Share Program Grants, 5 November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - DEQ - Rhinehart Tire Fire Superfund Site, Frederick County, 5 November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - DMV redesign of vehicle registration renewal form due to negative citizen and press reactions, 17 October 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Resources Authority (RVA) Bonds, 11 October 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - JMU property purchase of 983 Reservoir Street, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth Transportation Board Federal Highway Reimbursement Anticipation Notes, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - VHDA Housing Bonds, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ODU real estate transfer to ODU Real Estate Foundation, August 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DSS and DOE MOU to fund before and/or after-school programs, July 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DEM - Roanoke Tire Fire, July 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - William and Mary - Millington Hall, July 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DCR - rebuilding swimming pool at Pocahontas State Park in Chesterfield County, June 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Environmental Emergency Response Fund, June 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Tourism Authority - "Gods and Generals", June 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - NSU - Property Transfer of Williams Property to NSU Foundation, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - VPI and SU Variable Rate Revenue Bond Anticipation Note, June 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DSS - Combine Alexandria and Arlington Child Support Enforcement Offices, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DSS 10-year capital outlay lease for Child Support Enforcement in Fairfax, 23 April 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DHP - renew or initiate a 10-year capital outlay lease, 23 April 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Biotechnical Research Park Authority Variable Rate Revenue Bonds, 5 April 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - VCBA bond issue for the University of Richmond, 5 March 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - VCBA bond issue for the Shenandoah University, 5 March 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Use of Fort Pickett to train National Guard troops, 18 February 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2003
    - FEMA (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - GMU capital lease, 16 December 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - VEERF - Greenwood Chemical Superfund Site, 9 December 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Renovation of Finance and Washington Buildings (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School line of credit, 2 December 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Virginia College Building Authority (VCBA) Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds, November 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - DEM - disaster planning and operations, 20 November 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - DMME - BP Solarex - Solar Photovoltaic Manufacturing Incentive Program, 29 October 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Port Authority (VPA) - purchase of capital equipment, nd (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Resources Authority (VRA) Bonds,10 October 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - VHDA Rental Housing Bonds, 21 September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Distribution of Accelerated Sales Tax Revenues to Transportation Trust Fund, 9 September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - SCC legal expenses in Falwell v. Miller, 9 September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - DMV - 4th quarter interest earnings, August 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - General Obligation Bonds, 11 June 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General - civil commitment of sexually violent predators, 26 May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - DEM - water shortage in Buchanan and Tazewell counties, 8 May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Background to the Governor on options for establishing a program for civil commitment of sexually violent predators, May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - DEM - disaster planning and operations program, 8 May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Virginia College Building Authority (VCBA) Education Facilities Revenue Bonds, 8 May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Science Museum of Virginia - addition to the Danville Science Center project, April 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - DMHMRSAS - establish treatment program for civilly committed sexually violent predators, 9 April 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Visitors of GMU General Revenue Pledge Refunding Bonds, 14 April 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Rector and Visitors of UVA General Revenue Pledge Bonds, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - VHDA Bonds, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - VCU General Revenue Pledge Bonds, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Visitors of GMU General Revenue Pledge Bonds, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - VHDA Bonds, 10 February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue and Refunding Bonds, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 9C Higher Educational Institutions Bond Issuance Bill, 21 January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2004
    - Deficit loan to fund shortfall in Governor's Office and Cabinet offices, 5 January 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - VITA $6.1 million, 22 December 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Virginia College Building Authority (VCBA) Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds, December 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - VCCS - Tidewater Community College administrative offices in Norfolk, 6 January 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Department of Veterans Services - construction of storage facility at Roanoke Veterans Care Center, 4 January 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue Refunding Bonds, December 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - DJJ - Enlarge Bon Air Campus, 4 January 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - VHDA Tax-Exempt Rental Housing Bonds, 18 November 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - VDOT - replace administration building and wharf for Jamestown/Scotland Ferry due to severe damage caused by Hurricane Isabel in 2003, 16 November 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Obligation Bonds, November 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - City of Poquoson - Hurricane Isabel damage, 9 November 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Narbeth Borough Industrial Development Authority - Northwestern Human Services for mental health and mental retardation homes in Richmond and Virginia Beach, 29 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 27 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - DEM - Tropical Storm Gaston disaster costs, 25 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Department of Forestry - initiate capital improvements to accept three gifts of property, 25 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - DEM - Danville for tornado damage on 8-12-2004, 25 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - VCBA Series Bonds, October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - VRA Infrastructure Revenue Bond Series, 13 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - VMI Capital Project to acquire six parcels of land (North Main Street and Ruff Lane), 12 October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 15 September 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - DGS Capital Project - Bio Safety Lab, 15 September 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - VITA - positions increase, 15 September 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - VCU capital lease, 15 September 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - VMI Capital Project, 9 September 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - VHDA Bonds, 9 September 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - DEM - Severe Storms, 5-23-04, 3 September 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - VHDA Bonds Tax-exempt Single Family Housing, 31 August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue Refunding Bonds, August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - UVA Sports Medicine Facility, 26 August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Allocation of Interest Earning to Specific Nongeneral Fund Accounts, 26 August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Distribution of Accelerated Sales Taxes to Transportation Trust Fund, 26 August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - DGS - Real Estate Management Practices, 19 August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - DMHMRSAS - Inspector General increased funding, August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue Bonds, August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VCBA Bonds for University of Richmond, August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ABC - upgrade warehouse, July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - DEM - severe storm damage, 5-24-04, 23 July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - SBE - local reimbursements for 2004 Presidential Primary, July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General Obligation Bonds, July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VCBA Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds, July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Research at eight institutions of higher education, 13 July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lawrenceville Correctional Center, 13 July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VHDA Bond Issue, 12 July 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VCCS - 3% increase to the community college presidential salary scale, 21 June 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - DEM - Hurricane Isabel Recovery, May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - DEM - Tazewell Flood of 2001, May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VPI and SU Bond Package, May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - National World War II Veterans Memorial, 4 May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 4 May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - DEQ - Cost of Nitrogen Oxide Emission Auction, 16 April 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VHDA Bonds, 4 April 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Virginia Flood November 2003, 31 March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - UVA property transfer to UVA Foundation, March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Department of Veterans Services - cemetery administrator, 19 March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VCU General Revenue Pledge Refunding Bonds, March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority (MWAA) Revenue Bonds, 8 March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue Refunding Bonds, 8 March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Natural History Museum - executive director's salary, 1 March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 17 February 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Department for the Aging - moving office location, 17 February 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 2005
    - Enterprise Application Master Services Agreement with CGI-AMS, Inc., 30 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Portsmouth Campus Tidewater Community College land conveyance to Tidewater Community College Real Estate Foundation, 29 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VCU lease space in Theatre Row Building at 730 East Broad Street, 29 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VEC - Scope Change of Blanket Capital Project for Moving Expenses, 29 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - $20,000 death benefit authority by 2005 GA for state and local employees killed in Iraq or Afghanistan as reservists or National Guardsmen, 12 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - DMAS lease of office space at 600 East Broad Street, 12 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - State Police - Vansant area office purchase, 12 December 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - City of Virginia Beach - Oceana Air Station, 21 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 21 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VRA Bonds, 21 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 21 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VHDA Rental Housing Bonds, 18 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VHDA $800,000,000 Tax-Exempt Single-Family Housing Bonds, November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VPBA - financing for acquisition, construction, etc. of various public facilities for use by the Commonwealth, November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VCBA Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds, November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VPI Property Transfer to VaTech Foundation, 1 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VITA - "Generic" Enterprise Information Dashboard, 1 November 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Wise County and Big Stone Gap Water Shortage, 19 October 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Procurement Solution Contract with CGI-AMS, 26 September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Virginia National Guard's National Service Medal, 29 September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Revised Commonwealth Interoperability Strategic Plan, 29 September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - DOE/VCCS - disbursement plan to industry certification, 5 October 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - DOE - Phase 2 of NGA Grant, 5 October 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - DMAS - Emergency spending for victims of Hurricane Katrina, 5 October 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Administration - consolidated mail operations, 5 October 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - VCU Property Acquisition (Richmond Academy of Medicine), 5 October 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - VDOT - Federal Highway Reimbursement Anticipation Notes (FRANs), September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Institute of Forensic Science ($900,000) Training and Preparation for Scientist, 13 September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - VHDA Tax-Exempt, Multi-Family Rental Housing Bonds, 13 September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - DEM - Emergency Relief to Localities Program - Western Virginia Water Authority (Tropical Depression Jeanne), 13 September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Internet Quorum (IQ) Software, 30 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Department of Veterans Services at the Roanoke Veterans Care Center, 7 July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Beach land purchase, Near Post development on Laskin Road, 19 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Port Authority's extension of the 2003 Master Equipment Leasing Program, 5 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Rural and cultural economic development and tourism activities, 5 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Biotech Research Park Authority - Philip Morris Research and Technology Center, 5 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Modeling and Simulation Initiative (VIMSIM), 5 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - City of Poquoson - Hurricane Isabel Costs, 5 August 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - DOC - web-enabled inventory system for prison warehouses, July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - State agency leases at Forest Office Park in Henrico County, July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - VSBFA Bonds - Briarwood Holdings and Southern Virginia University, July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - DSS - Low Income Energy Assistance Program, 25 July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - VDOT lease extension for Northern Virginia District Office, 17 July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - JMU transfer of real estate to JMU Foundation, July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - UVA Bonds, July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Roanoke Veterans Care Center Renovations, 7 July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - William and Mary Preston Hall restoration (dorm fire), July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Enterprise Applications Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act (PPEA), 12 July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Portsmouth Marine Terminal, 12 July 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - GMU to purchase land in Prince William County for Regional Biocontainment Laboratory, 19 July 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VHDA Bonds, May 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VCBA Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds, May 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VRA Bonds for Prince William County, May 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VCBA Bond Issue for Hampton University, May 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Health - Reengineering authorized onsite soil evaluators program, March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - DEM - Southwest Virginia Flood of November 2003, 26 April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority - Commonwealth Port Fund Revenue Bonds, April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VHDA Rental Housing Bonds, 13 April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VSBFA Bonds, 13 April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue Refunding Bonds, April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Frontier Culture Museum - three new positions, 13 April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - VPA Commonwealth Port Fund Revenue Refunding Bonds, 13 April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - VHDA Rental Housing Bonds for Single-Family Housing, March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DCR - electronic ranger kiosks and undercover surveillance units, denied 23 March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DMV - reengineering existing correspondence system, denied 23 March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - VPBA Public Facilities Revenue Refunding Bonds, March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DOC - purchase of land adjacent to VCE Distribution Center, 16 March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - VHDA Tax-Exempt Rental Housing Bonds, March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DMME energy account funds to alternate provider, 4 March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DSP - reengineer Amber Alert system, 4 March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Workforce Development - Career Readiness Certificate Program, 25 February 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DHRM - Statewide Recruitment Management System, 24 February 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, 24 February 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DEM - Tropical Depression Jeanne, 24 February 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DHCD - develop and implement e-government database system, 24 February 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - State Board of Elections, 21 January 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DMME - Electronic Permitting and Reporting System, 18 January 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - JMU 20-year lease with Harrisonburg for basketball arena and baseball stadium, 18 January 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9 c Bond Bill for 2005 Session, 18 January 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- II. Regulations, 2002-2006 (accession 42413)., Extent: 12.25 cubic feet (34 boxes). (Box 4-37)
  The Regulations series is housed in 34 boxes and is arranged by cabinet secretary and alphabetically by state agency therein. The series consists of regulation review forms, memorandums, recommendations, and summary of regulations.